We'll be right back.
Cannon fire is the signal.
CP-9 goes into action.
!
Califa?
Yes, Mr. Iceberg?
Not to be rude, but do you mind stepping out of the room for a moment?
No, of course not.
One more thing.
Fetch Pauly.
I need to have a word with him.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, Polly.
Mr. Iceberg needs to see you.
I assume it's very important.
He asked for me?
Yes, specifically.
I have some things to take care of in my office if anyone needs me.
Right.
Seems like awfully strange timing for a one-on-one conversation.
What in blazes could it be about?
Don't have a clue.
It's his will!
Well, what are you doing out here?
Go on in there and talk to him.
Uh, sure.
Don't worry. We can step away from the door if you're concerned about privacy.
Good idea.
What the heck could he want to talk about with Polly?
Whatever it is, it's between them.
We got enough to deal with.
I think we need to stay focused on our pirate problem.
Right.
Okay, according to Polly,
it's a small group with only seven people on their crew.
The ones to watch out for are Straw Hat Luffy,
Pirate Hunter Zorro,
and Nico Rabbit.
I wouldn't underestimate the girl traveling along with them,
or that other guy with the long, round nose.
Yeah.
There are those two you just mentioned,
along with two others.
Cuckoo!
It doesn't matter what those pirates are after.
They set foot on this property tonight,
they're done for.
Every single last one of them.
Got it?
Cuckoo!
Right!
Yeah, I understand, sir.
I apologize for putting you in harm's way like this, Polly.
But this is a very grave matter,
and I trust you can get it done.
Can I put my faith in you?
I give you my word, sir.
I swear, I won't let you down.
You're a good man.
Well, suppose I should get on it.
Thank you.
Cuckoo!
Ain't I talking with you?
Yeah.
Hey, listen, guys.
I gotta head out and take care of something.
Cool?
No problem.
That'll be fine.
The four of us will keep watch over things here.
Thanks.
Just keep Iceberg safe, you guys.
When you leave here,
go straight to my office and move my desk.
I want you to lift up the rug and look underneath it.
There's a safe hidden there.
Jackpot.
Once you find that, enter this combination.
First, ride to number six.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Awaiting your signal.
It will be very soon now.
At that time, the four of you are to carry out your respective missions with ruthless efficiency.
As a loyal member of CP-9, you have my word.
Nico Robin, are you ready?
Yes.
I am.
Whoa!
Something blew up!
Huh?
Oh, no.
What the hell was that?
Grab water now!
We got a man down over here!
Make sure that fire doesn't spread to the building!
Guys, they're shooting at us!
No, man.
I'm pretty sure it was some kind of bomb.
Someone must have said it, then.
Hurry, men!
We gotta put out this fire!
Someone give me a hand!
Not too subtle, but it'll do.
Let's move.
The fire's in the north corner of the first floor.
Has anyone heard?
There have been no pirates spotted yet!
Everyone keep your eyes peeled for intruders!
Stay at your post, men!
Don't let them get inside!
Iceberg, are you okay?
Yeah.
Just a bit shocked.
There they are!
Huh?
It's that guy in the costume!
Get him!
Those bastards!
Rawr!
All pounding their faces!
I got you, Matt!
Wait!
Hold on!
For Pete's sake.
There he goes!
Hurry!
We got this clown!
He's alone!
Locks him in!
Stop!
It's the end of the line!
He's heading for the roof!
So you thought you could get away, didn't you, punk?
It's gonna take a lot more than that to get by us.
You made a big mistake when you decided to mess with Galilaw.
Prepare for the beating of your life!
Because we're not gonna show any mercy, scumbag!
You can come at me with all you've got, but it still won't be enough.
We've got two over here!
We're headed for the back door!
Try and corner them!
Boom!
Move!
After them!
Don't let those bastards get inside!
You have the floor plan memorized.
Is that correct?
Yes.
So, they all seem pretty worked up down there.
Yeah.
There's definitely something going on right now.
All right, then.
When are we gonna make our move?
Hey, where's Luffy?
Ah!
That idiot!
What about the plan?
I thought we weren't gonna rush into anything!
Too late.
They're going for the back door!
Let's head them off!
No matter what, they can't get inside!
You got a lot of nerve coming here after the crap you tried to pull last night!
You're gonna pay for what you did!
Oh, yeah!
You guys are in for a world of hurt for messing with Mr. Iceberg!
Surrender!
Give it up now, and we might just go easy on you!
You're surrounded!
There's nowhere to run!
We already know it's not just the two of you guys and your little pirate gang!
Now, where are the others?
He's pulling out a weapon!
Shoot him!
No way!
They're gone!
What the hell?
Where'd they go?
Hey, are you okay?
Man, that guy's a monster!
He flew!
He was flying through the air!
What the hell?
He can fly?
Idiots, do you not know when to give up?
He's jumping!
Moonwalk!
What the?
He's really flying!
Thorny Road!
I told you you were bested, didn't I?
Get ready!
Here he comes!
He's gonna land in the courtyard!
Don't let him escape!
There he goes!
Get around him!
We can trap him in there!
Yeah!
This is it.
Interesting.
All this time, it was literally right under our noses.
Hand it over.
You can't possibly understand its importance.
Who are you bastards?
Where in the hell did you come from?
From the shadows.
Yes.
From the darkest corners of existence, we bring with us the light of justice.
We are Cypher Pole No. 9, an undercover intelligence agency.
Well, no matter where you freaks came from, you sure as hell didn't get in without running
into the galley log craftsmen.
Perhaps we did.
The details are all very hazy.
A sea of fists and bodies.
What's important is we're here now.
I get it.
This ain't just some assassination plot, is it?
Very astute.
But then we never claimed that it was, now did we?
In any case, we need what Iceberg was trying to keep hidden, the item you hold in your trembling
hand, now, and since you've been made aware of its existence, we need to take your life
as well.
Entrusting you to this task, Iceberg has signed your death warrant.
What's the word?
Did you find him?
Nuh-uh.
There's no sign of those guys anywhere.
They get inside?
There's men standing guard at every single point of entry.
No, there's no way they got in.
Damn it.
Where the hell did they go?
They couldn't have gotten far.
They've got to be hiding somewhere.
Search the perimeter one more time.
Got it?
Yeah!
疲れ果てた向きの中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつか辿り着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に
見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸辿り 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた羽渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に 永遠に
永遠にもここに 中で オーブンに挑戦してくれ きょう 王硬
順番とも相差しなり Where do you mean?
即してよく近いことはずっとあることが大皿に
ほんとに生後すると 取測ししても Godを見て principio
この一いかが 残ってるからじゃ 生死は残った âが二次
コンボフィスやシテ2・なる何 役中のカフェスが近い
え 그럼 Bendidade indicating 中度に戻まずは nobody
見 Jakesyをさせた所 이런 雰囲って
戦画だよ
You